# Tolulope Babatunde

Full Stack Developer

39 Ondo street Bodija,

Ibadan, Oyo

Nigeria,

babatundetolulopejoshua@yahoo.com 07041147115

Passionate Software Engineer with over 5 years experience in front-end (web and mobile) and back-end development, with a particular interest in using javascript-based libraries and frameworks to create high-performance software applications. Seeks a position where he can provide technical expertise while improving professional competence.

## **Professional Experience**

### **Software Developer**

#### Ehealth4everyone | July 2023 - Present

- Design client-side and server-side architecture
- Develop desktop and mobile applications
- Develop and manage well-functioning databases and applications
- Work with development teams and product managers to improve software
- Use Git tools for codebase management

#### **Software Developer**

#### Cytix IO | June 2022 - December 2022

- Build features and applications with a mobile responsive design
- Build the front-end of applications through appealing visual design
- Attend weekly meetings and discussions.

#### **Full Stack Developer**

#### Freelance | January 2018 - June 2022

- Build, troubleshoot, debug and upgrade software
- Write effective APIs
- Test software to ensure responsiveness and efficiency
- Create security and data protection settings

### **Education**

#### **B.Tech in Physics**

Federal University of Technology at Akure | January 2010 - January 2015

# **Key Skills**

- Knowledge of front-end languages and libraries (HTML/CSS, Bootstrap/Tailwindcss, Javascript, Jquery, Typescript)
- Knowledge of multiple back-end languages (Node.js, Java Spring Boot and Python Django) and Javascript frameworks (React, Vue)
- Familiarity with databases (MySQL, MongoDB), web servers and UI/UX design
- Excellent communication and teamwork
- Great attention to details
- Excellent analytical and multitasking skills

### **Portfolio**

https://tolulopejoshua.github.io